Guide to the Philip G. Zimbardo Papers SC0750
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Publications and writing, Series 4
  - Papers and articles
    - "From Marginal Deviations to Growth in Aggression: A Cross-National Investigation," / Caprara, Dodge, Gerbino, Pastorelli, Zelli, Zimbardo (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - "Social Psychology: Tool for Improving the Human Condition," / Zimbardo, Luce (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Ebbesen / Zimbardo - JEAB (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - "The Objective Measurement of Subjective States," Zimbardo / Ebbesen (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Conjugate Reinf. Results (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - "The Objective Measurement of Subjective States: Externalizing Internal Disposition," / Zimbardo, Ebbesen (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - "Aggregation and Amplification of Marginal Deviations in the Social Construction of Personality and Maladjustment," / Caprara, Zimbardo (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - "Evil's Seven Step Seduction Scenario," / Zimbardo (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - "Not to Be Seen, But Need to Be Noticed," / Zimbardo, 2006 (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Articles by Zimbardo (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Articles about Zimbardo (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - Chapter for Robert Arkin (Ed.). "Saga of Mys Stealth Bomber Chapter: Can't Miss, But Vanished Without a Trace," / Zimbardo (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - "Celebrating Heroism: A Conceptual Exploration," / Franco, Blau, Zimbardo (Box 156, Folder 26)
    - "Liberating Behavior from Time-Bound Control: Expanding the Present Through Hypnosis," Zimbardo, Marshall, Maslach (Box 156, Folder 27)
    - Op-Ed Cults (Box 156, Folder 28)
    - Yosemite Paper (Box 156, Folder 29)
    - Reviews of Zimbardo works (Box 156, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Research files, Series 5
  Dr. Zimbardo performed psychological research in a number of areas and maintained files on his many research interests including most notably: burnout; hypnosis; madness; persuasion; prisons; shyness; time; and violence/evil. Other files include miscellaneous subject files organized alphabetically and files relating to studies performed by Zimbardo.
  The materials in these files include clippings, articles, bibliographic research, and notes. Also present in this series are data, journals, and notes related to research studies.
  Files are arranged into subseries by research topic, which include: burnout; hypnosis; madness; persuasion; prisons; shyness; studies; subject files; time; and violence/evil.
  - Burnout
    - Depression & Burnout (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Measurement of Experienced Burnout, Maslach & Jackson (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Berkeley Survey of Professional Occupations-Burnout Study, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Staff Burnout Articles (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Burnout & Political Activists (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Burnout & Service Workers Articles (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Burnout Articles (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Burnout Articles (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Burnout Journals, 1984-1986 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Burnout Articles (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Burnout (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Maslach Burnout Inventory (MBI) (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - MBI Annotations (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Burnout & Sex Differences (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Burnout & Stress (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Burnout Theories/Measurement (1 of 4) (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Burnout Theories/Measurement (2 of 4) (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Burnout Theories/Measurement (3 of 4) (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Burnout Theories/Measurement (4 of 4) (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Burnout & Teachers (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Burnout & Volunteers (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Burnout & Librarians (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Burnout in Government Agencies (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Burnout & Human Services (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Maslach Burnout Research (1 of 5) (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Maslach Burnout Research (2 of 5) (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Maslach Burnout Research (3 of 5) (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Maslach Burnout Research (4 of 5) (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Maslach Burnout Research (5 of 5) (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Burnout Articles (1 of 3) (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Burnout Articles (2 of 3) (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Burnout Articles (3 of 3) (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Stats: Professor Sex & Ethnicity (Maslach), 1983-1987 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Burnout and AIDS workers (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Burnout book-first drafts (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Burnout-new refs and ideas (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Burnout (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Burnout-misc. articles (1 of 7) (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Burnout-misc. articles (2 of 7) (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Burnout-misc. articles (3 of 7) (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Burnout-misc. articles (4 of 7) (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Burnout-misc. articles (5 of 7) (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Burnout-misc. articles (6 of 7) (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Burnout-misc. articles (7 of 7) (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Burnout-Maslach (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Maslach-Burnout (1 of 2) (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Maslach-Burnout (2 of 2) (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Pubs-Burnout (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Burnout-lecture material (1 of 2) (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Burnout-lecture material (2 of 2) (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - ENOP Conference-Burnout, Krakow, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - C. Maslach. "Burned out Samaritans," Human Behavior, 1976 Sep (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - C. Maslach. "Burned out Samaritans," Human Behavior, 1976 Sep (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Pubs-Burnout (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Hypnosis
    - Heart Rate (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Tabulations Results (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - EA Data (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Motive Attribution Study (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Research on Motive Attribution, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Motive Attribution Research, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Research: NEW-madness (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Hypnosis and the Psychology of Cognitive and Behavioral Control, 1970 Nov (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Research: Hypnosis Training Report (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Hypnosis Research...Forms used for Z/A/K Study (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Publications: Predicting Cognitive Processes from Social Behavior: Classroom Seating, Hypnotizability, and Cognitive Style. R. Montero & PGZ., 1985 Sep (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Hypnosis: Confidential Medical History Form, Informed Consent, Personal Impression Form, 1980 Feb 22 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Harvard Group Scale of Hypnotic Susceptibility. Instructions., 1988 Fall (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Hypnosis Training (6 sessions) 2 copies (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Hypnosis...Intro to Introduction (copy) Harvard Group Scale (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Harvard Group Scale (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Cognitive Control & Hypnosis (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Hypnotizability Scale (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Harvard Group Scale of Hypnotic Susceptibility...Induction Booklet, Response Booklet. Psych 001, S85/86, 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - SCEH Presentation (Hypnosis & Discontinuity) (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Research: Hypnosis-Possible Ss for F, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Piccione-1. Hypnosis, 1985 Apr 1 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Hypnosis Research-F, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Lynette Silva, 11:15 (S #32), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Jen Barton, 12:30 (S#31), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Sibyl Diver, 12:00 (S#30), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Karen Pena, 10:30 (S#29), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Lisa Rampton, 10:00 (S#28), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Will Kuntz, 5:15 (S#27), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Scott Minkow, 4:30 (S#26), 1993 Mar 10 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Bill Tsiokos, 4:00 (S#25), 1993 Mar 10 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Patrick Kenny, 12:30 (S#24), 1993 Mar 11 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Sung Hwan Cho, 4:30 (S#23), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Matt Krusinski, 2:30 (S#22), 1993 Mar 10 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Dulce Scavone, 2:00 (S#21), 1993 Mar 10 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Andre Javier, 12:00 (S#20), 1993 Mar 9 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Aron Buckles, 11:30 (S#19), 1993 Mar 9 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Chris McCaslin, 11:00 (S#18), 1993 Mar 9 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Iris Kedar, 10:00 (S#17), 1993 Mar 9 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Sarah Novasel, 2:30 (S#16), 1993 Mar 8 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Tracy Cieskwicz, 1:30 (S#15), 1993 Mar 8 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Cara Rice, 1:00 (S#14), 1993 Mar 8 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - Amy Storey, 2:30 (S#13), 1993 Mar 3 (Box 50, Folder 43)
    - Debbie Adler, 2:00 (S#12), 1993 Mar 3 (Box 50, Folder 44)
    - Jessica Mega, 1:30 (S#11), 1993 Mar 3 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Matt Parsons, 12:30 (S#9), 1993 Mar 2 (Box 50, Folder 46)
    - Jennifer Datton, 12:00(S#8), 1993 Mar 2 (Box 50, Folder 47)
    - Barry McMillion, 11:30 (S#7), 1993 Mar 2 (Box 50, Folder 48)
    - Mark Brandt, 11:00 (S#6), 1993 Mar 2 (Box 50, Folder 49)
    - LaShaun Williams, 3:00 (S#5), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 50)
    - Ira Parghi, 10:00 (S#4), 1993 Mar 2 (Box 50, Folder 51)
    - Megan Curren, 3:45 (S#3), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 52)
    - Anne Schuckman, 1:30 (#2), 1993 Mar 1 (Box 50, Folder 53)
    - Andrea Webber, 1:00 (#1), 1993 Mar 1 (Box 50, Folder 54)
    - Michael Adedipe, 2:00 (S#34), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 55)
    - Adam Myhre, 1:30 (S#33), 1993 Mar 12 (Box 50, Folder 56)
    - Solo Creativity Task, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 57)
    - Forms Used for Control Study, 1993 May (Box 50, Folder 58)
    - Debriefing, 1993 Mar (Box 50, Folder 59)
    - 3 Bias Study, Transcript Duplicates-Explained, 1985 Sep 18 (Box 50, Folder 60)
    - 3 Bias Study, Transcripts (Duplicates) -Body, 1985 Jul 30 (Box 50, Folder 61)
    - Time-Hypnosis Sign up (Box 50, Folder 62)
    - Subject Scheduling (RA Info) (Box 50, Folder 63)
    - Personal Relaxation Imagery & Training Sessions 1&2 (Box 50, Folder 64)
    - Confed Rating (confed 1) (Box 50, Folder 65)
    - Confed Rating (confed 2) (Box 50, Folder 66)
    - Anagrams (Box 50, Folder 67)
    - MMPI Scoring Info (Box 50, Folder 68)
    - Task 2, Part 2 (Box 50, Folder 69)
    - Personal Impression Form (Box 50, Folder 70)
    - Discontinuity Study (Box 50, Folder 71)
    - Post-Exp. Follow ups (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - T1, P1- TAT 1 (Box 50, Folder 73)
    - T2, P2 - TAT 1 (Box 50, Folder 74)
    - Mood Adjective Checklist (empty) (Box 50, Folder 75)
    - Questionnaires for Exp Session, Hyp/Dsicon. S. Andersen (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - Forms for Excluded Ss (Box 50, Folder 77)
    - Mood Adjective Checklist (Box 50, Folder 78)
    - SHSS:C Deafness Suggestion (Box 50, Folder 79)
    - Originals for Slides for Hypnosis Study (Box 50, Folder 80)
    - Hypnosis/Discontinuity-->Scripts/Forms (Box 50, Folder 81)
    - Anagrams (Box 50, Folder 82)
    - Task 1, Part 1 (Box 50, Folder 83)
    - Task 1, Part 2 (Box 50, Folder 84)
    - Task 2, Part 1 (Box 50, Folder 85)
    - Hypochondriasis, MMPA Scoring Keys (Box 50, Folder 86)
    - MMPI-Post (Box 50, Folder 87)
    - MMPI-Pre (Box 50, Folder 88)
    - PIF- Paranoia (Box 50, Folder 89)
    - PIF- Paranoia (After) (Box 50, Folder 90)
    - Hypnosis (correspondences) (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Hypnosis Research Bibliography (empty) (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Personal Impression Form-blank (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Extra Confed. Scripts (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - T2,P2- TAT 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Hypnosis: Personal Experience Evaluation & Answer Sheet for ---//--- (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Human Subjects-Proposals-Emotional Arousal, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - New Res. Rational Analysis of Emotional Arousal, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Motivational/Emotional Controls of Cognition, H. A. Simon, Psych. Review, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Hypnotic Control of Skin Temperature, 1972 Jun 8 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Tempo Modification--Science Article (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Incentive, Time Conception & Self Control in a Group of Emotionally Disturbed Boys-Levine & Spivack, 1959 Jan (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Action of Adrenaline on Emotions Study by G. Maranon, in Revue Fran., D'Endocrinologie 2, 5, October 1924 (translated to English, 1972), 1924 Oct (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Intro. Cognitive Control, conclusion, 1968 Feb (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Hypnosis & Psych of Cognitive and Behavioral Control, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Tempo Study (various materials) (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Time Distortion Under Hypnosis, by Zimbardo, Marshall, White (1), 1972 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Time Distortion Under Hypnosis, by Zimbardo, Marshall, White (2), 1972 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Hypnosis/discontinuity-slides for Exp. Session (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - T2, P1; TAT-2 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Personal Experience Evaluation (Booklet & Answer sheet) (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Personal Experience Evaluation (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Final Survey (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Final Survey Form #3 (empty) (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Future Work Form (hypnosis work) (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Rater's Evaluation (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Tempo Study (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Tempo Modification (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Analyses-Tempo & Distortion (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Research Projects, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Hypnosis and Control Paper (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Hypnosis Training Schedules (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Hypnosis Research: Stanford Personality Inventory: Version E, 1985 Mar 6 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Hypnosis Training: Session 2, Instructors Evaluation, Post-debriefing Eval., 1985 Feb 13 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Hypnosis Research Form 2:85-7, Informed Consent Form, 1985 Mar 14 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Hypnosis Research Form 2:85-1, Enhancement Traning Z/P (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Hypnosis Research Form 2:85-2, Battery of Personality Tests Z/L/P (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Hypnosis Research Form 2:85-3, Varied hypnotic suggestions Z/P/L (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Stanford Personality Inventory, short form, 1985 Feb (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Hypnosis Research: 5 Personal Letters, 1985 Mar 27 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Hypnosis Session #1 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Hypnosis Forms (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Hypnosis Forms (2) (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Spegel- Hypnosis and Law/Confessions, 1968 Aug (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Lab. of Hypnosis Research, Project Status Report, 1964 Oct (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Survey of Objective Studies of Psychoanalytic Concepts, 1943 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Profile Scales of Hypnotic Susceptibility (2 books), 1963 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Medical Uses of Hypnosis (2 books), Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry, 1962 Apr (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Hypnosis/EEG, Subject 1, 1989 May-1989 Jun (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Hypnosis/EEG, Subject 2, 1989 May-1989 Jun (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Hypnosis/EEG, Subject 3, 1989 May-1989 Jun (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Hypnosis/EEG, Subject 4, 1989 May-1989 Jun (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Health Forms, PB Study, 1986 Spring (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - WAI- Ss, PB Study, 1986 Spring (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Complete Personal Letters, PB Study, 1986 May-1986 Jun (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Completed Release of Data, PB Study, 1986 May (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Complete Informed Consent, PB Study, 1986 May (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Pre-experiment Instructions, Raw Data, PB Study, 1986 May (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Consent Forms Experiment, PB Study, 1986 May (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Consent Forms, Data Release, PB Study, 1986 May (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Consent Forms, Hypnosis Training, Blanks, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Consent Forms, Unused Ss, Hyp Training, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - 3-Bias Study Consent Forms, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Hypnotic Research Consent Forms, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Release of Data Consent Forms, Raw Data, 3-Bias, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Hypnosis/Emotion (recent studies of post-hypnotic amnesia), 1971 Oct (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Hypnosis Articles (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Hypnosis Articles (2) (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Hypnosis Articles (3) (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Hypnosis Consent Forms, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Hypnosis Susceptibility Scoring (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Hypnosis Susceptibility Scoring (2) (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Unit II-Sex Differences-health, sex, personality, social cognition (1 of 3) (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Test 2 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Psychology 130-Stanford in Florence, 1983/1984 Autumn (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Psychology 130-Sex Roles-Stanford in Florence, 1983/1984 Autumn (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Hypnosis articles (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Hypnosis release forms-unexplained arousal (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Hypnosis research-U.C. (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Hypnosis articles (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Hilgard-A Saga of Hypnosis, 1979 Sept. (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - A Syllabus on Hypnosis (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Hypnosis reader (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - Hypnosis reader-appendices (1 of 3) (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - Hypnosis reader-appendices (2 of 3) (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - Hypnosis reader-appendices (3 of 3) (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - Harvard Group Scale of Hypnotic Susceptibility (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - Harvard Group Scale of Hypnotic Susceptibility, 1988 Oct 6 (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - Harvard Group Scale of Hypnotic Susceptibility (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - Hypnosis (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - Hypnosis Training Program (1 of 2) (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - Hypnosis Training Program (2 of 2) (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - Hypnosis studies-interview transcripts (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - Hypnosis conference-APA Board of Directors retreat, 2002 Apr 19-21 (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - Hypnosis-APA, 2001 (Box 146, Folder 35)
    - Hypnosis convention-summary of all our studies (Box 146, Folder 36)
    - Hypnosis (emotion, time, temp.) original figures (Box 146, Folder 37)
    - Hypnosis articles (Box 146, Folder 38)
    - SCEH-Hypnosis, 1981 (Box 146, Folder 39)
  - Madness
    - Maslach/Unexplained Arousal (madness, discontinuity research), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - "Assessment of Reactions to Anomalous Events" (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - RESEARCH-Analysis Emotional Arousal, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Madness Class Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Madness (Personal Account-Media), 1977 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - RESEARCH: Explanations of Unexpected Experiences (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Madness Models (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Articles (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Relevant Articles to Discontuity (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Discontinuity/Madness Library Filing (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Normal Madness, Circa 1977 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Madness Filing, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - SUA Scale (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Self-Disclosure (articles) (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Articles (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - 6-Month Follow-up Summary (3-Bias), 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - 3-Bias Study (Transcript Duplicates- People), 1985 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - 3-Bias Study, Transcript Duplciates, no bias, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - 3-Bias Study, Transcript duplicates-Environment (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Pre-Experimental Self-Report (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Physio Bias Study Results, New, 1987 Jul (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Computer Printouts, DVs (ParQ), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - SUA Control, Physio bias (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - SUA Ratings, Physio Bias, 1987 Aug (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Exner, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Grant- Drafts, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Hypnosis Stuff for Rosanne, Draft of Transcripts/Evaluations (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Original Transcripts, Stanford Ss (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Discontinuting Scoring Systems (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - PB Study Notes, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Clinical Ratings, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Clinical Observations CUMS, Madness, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Clinical Observation Forms, VA, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - State & Trait Manual Endler, Anxiety Mesasures/Physio Bias, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Stat. Tables (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Madness (newspaper clippings), 1976 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Preliminary Ideas Toward a Model of Madness, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - SUA-PB Study, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Hypnosis Testing Subject Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Tables/Graphs Madness, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Tables/Graphs, PB Study, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - Discontinutiy Original Study Manual (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Hypnosis Training Instructions, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - Mad Overheads, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Typed Procedures, PB Study, 1986 Spring (Box 64, Folder 45)
    - How do friends define me as mentally ill? P.Smith-Interview, Discontinuity, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 46)
    - Research Record/Observations, Zimbardo, 1985-1989 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Data Analysis Printouts, PB Physio (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Madness Readings (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Madness + Rationality/APA, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Publication: Induced Meaninglessness-Ethics Letterw/ back up in APA, 1981-1983 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Research: Madness-Correspondence, Circa 1974 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Deafness/Paranoia Data Table, 1981 Apr (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Research-Madness (general), 1975 Mar (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Research: Hypnosis & Discontinuity, 1987 Oct 31 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Discont./Hearing and Paranoia Exp. Procedure (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - The Modification of Selective Recall of Central & Incidental Task Features by Emotional Arousal, by A. Schiffenbauer, S. Sherman, and P. Zimbardo, 1970 May (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Madness Binder #2: Transcripts from Discontinuity Study, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Madness Binder #2: NIMH Grant Proposal, Complete copy including Budget and Bios. all appedices + the reprints of Appendix E-File copy (ethics), 1986 Jan 29 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Madness Binder #2: Discontinuity Study-BODY, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Madness Binder #2: Discontinuity Study-PEOPLE, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Madness Binder #2: Discontinuity Study-ENVIRONMENT, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Madness Binder #2: Discontinuity Study-NO BIAS, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Madness Binder #2: Discontinuity Study-EXPLAINED, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Madness Binder #2: Discontinuity Study-NOTES, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - 3 Bias Study, Discontinuity Transcripts, Pre-Post Evaluation (Zimbardo, Piccione)-PEOPLE, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - 3 Bias Study, Discontinuity Transcripts, Pre-Post Evaluation (Zimbardo, Piccione)-BODY, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - 3 Bias Study, Discontinuity Transcripts, Pre-Post Evaluation (Zimbardo, Piccione)-ENVIRONMENT, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - 3 Bias Study, Discontinuity Transcripts, Pre-Post Evaluation (Zimbardo, Piccione)-NO BIAS, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - 3 Bias Study, Discontinuity Transcripts, Pre-Post Evaluation (Zimbardo, Piccione)-EXPLAINED, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - 3 Bias Study, Discontinuity Transcripts, Pre-Post Evaluation (Zimbardo, Piccione)-DISCARDS, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Discontinuity, 3 Bias Study, 6 mo. later follow-up, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - 3 Bias Study Research Assistants, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - 3 Bias Study Procedure, Forms, Results (Zimbardo, Piccione)-HUMAN SUBJECTS COMMITTEE, 1985 Jan 14 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - 3 Bias Study Procedure, Forms, Results (Zimbardo, Piccione)-PRE-EXPERIMENT, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - 3 Bias Study Procedure, Forms, Results (Zimbardo, Piccione)-HYPNOSIS TRAINING, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - 3 Bias Study Procedure, Forms, Results (Zimbardo, Piccione)-THE EXPERIMENT, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - 3 Bias Study Procedure, Forms, Results (Zimbardo, Piccione)-FORMS & TESTS, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - 3 Bias Study Procedure, Forms, Results (Zimbardo, Piccione)-RESULTS, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 33)